but there are also more options available.
So I can click this More button and over here,
if I want GPT to create me an image,
I can use this one so I can click on it and it will be on,
on this very message, you know, so it's an option, something like that.
Or I can open this thing up and say shopping research, right?
So I will give chat GPT more context of the concept I'm talking about.
You know, so if it's about shopping, for example, this car thing,
I want to buy it, right?
So by clicking on shopping research, it will go deeper.
So cars may not be an appropriate example,
but for example, when I'm searching for clothes,
when I'm searching for smaller products, you know, mugs, etc.
I will be able to turn this on as well.
I can come here and click the pre-search, so chat GPT will take its time.
And we'll think way more than usual on the very command that I give it.
So this is the deep research option.
We also can click thinking.